[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the movie Hoosiers released?", "correct_answer": "1986", "incorrect_answers": ["1982", "1972", "1975"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why doesnt the IRA hitman shoot Dwight in the film Sin City?", "correct_answer": "He wants to blow him up.", "incorrect_answers": ["Hes Dwights friend from prison.", "His gun gets wet in the sewer.", "Dwight falls on his head."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the ideal popping temperature for popcorn?", "correct_answer": "330\u00b0-380\u00b0 F (165\u00b0-193\u00b0C)", "incorrect_answers": ["500\u00b0-560\u00b0 F(260\u00b0-293\u00b0C)", "260\u00b0-310\u00b0 F(127\u00b0-154\u00b0C)", "400\u00b0-460\u00b0 F(204\u00b0-238\u00b0C)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the movie Next Friday released?", "correct_answer": "2000", "incorrect_answers": ["2002", "1999", "2001"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a Swiss chocolate manufacturer?", "correct_answer": "Hersheys", "incorrect_answers": ["Suchard", "Nestle", "Lindt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chef Wolfgang Puck is of German descent.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the following terms mean one and the same thing - fear of storms. Which is the forth one that is related to sleep?", "correct_answer": "Clinophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Keraunophobia", "Brontophobia", "Astraphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You can go to jail for intentionally killing a praying mantis as it is an endangered species.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first nation to become Christian?", "correct_answer": "Armenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Antioch", "Romania", "Rome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most important ingredient for preparing brownies, a type of American dessert?", "correct_answer": "Chocolate", "incorrect_answers": ["Coffee", "Brown sugar", "Molasses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the science of colors called?", "correct_answer": "Chromatics", "incorrect_answers": ["Chromatology", "Colorology", "Coloritics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the opening scene of the movie Forrest Gump, Forrest is sitting on a bench waiting to catch a bus in what southern U.S. city?", "correct_answer": "Savannah", "incorrect_answers": ["Birmingham", "Atlanta", "Columbia"]}]